<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">BeckFowler</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Configurações</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="kent_beck">Kent Beck</string>
    <string name="kent_beck_description">Kent Beck is an American software engineer and the creator of the Extreme Programming and Test Driven Development software development methodologies, also named agile software development. Beck was one of the 17 original signatories of the Agile Manifesto in 2001. He attended the University of Oregon between 1979 and 1987, receiving B.S. and M.S. degrees in computer science. He has pioneered software design patterns, the rediscovery of test-driven development, as well as the commercial application of Smalltalk. Beck popularized CRC cards with Ward Cunningham and along with Erich Gamma created the JUnit unit testing framework. Beck lives near Medford, Oregon and works at Facebook (Text and photo from Wikipedia)</string>
	<string name="martin_fowler_name">Martin Fowler</string>
	<string name="martin_fowler_description">Martin Fowler is a British software engineer, author and international speaker on software development, specializing in object-oriented analysis and design, UML, patterns, and agile software development methodologies, including extreme programming. He introduced Model View ViewModel (MVVM) - an architectural pattern. Fowler was born and grew up in Walsall, England, where he went to Queen Mary\'s Grammar School for his secondary education. He graduated at University College London in 1986. In 1994 he moved to the United States, where he lives near Boston, Massachusetts in the suburb of Melrose. Fowler started working with software in the early 1980s. Out of college in 1986 he started working in software development for Coopers and Lybrand until 1991. In 2000 he became Chief Scientist at ThoughtWorks, a systems integration and consulting company. Fowler has written seven books on the topic of software development. He is a member of the Agile Alliance and helped create the Manifesto for Agile Software Development in 2001, along with more than 15 co-authors. He maintains a bliki, a mix of blog and wiki. He popularized the term Dependency Injection as a form of Inversion of Control (Text and photo from Wikipedia).</string>
</resources>
